Yes, Leah.
はい、リアちゃん
yes.
はい
Let's put it inside for a moment.
ちょっとそれ、中入れてみようか
Can't get in?
入らない?
It might not come in.
入らないかもしれない
Ah, it's in.
あ、入ってるね
it hurts?
痛い?
See you soon.
じゃあね、もう
Let's try our best to the best of our ability.
頑張れるところまで頑張ってみようか
Once you put it in, I want you to keep it there.
入れたら、そこでキープしてほしい
Let's try our best to keep it.
頑張ってキープしてみよう
It hurts, isn't it?
痛いよね
Can you keep it here?
ここでさ、キープできる?
Oh, or rather, I'm keeping it.
あ、というか、俺がキープしてるのか、
I.
俺
Yeah, that's what it feels like, that's what it feels like.
そうそう、そんな感じ、そんな感じ
I'll try my best and get it inside.
ちょっと頑張って、中を取りますよ
I can do a little bit of this myself.
こっちの身もちょこっちできる
Good, good.
いいね、いいね
Wow, it's pure white.
うわー、真っ白ですね
pure white?
真っ白?
Yeah.
うん
Is it pure white?
真っ白なの?
pure white.
真っ白
I'm drinking my spirit now.
もう、精神飲みる
Yeah.
うん
I'm just going to move it a little bit, just a little bit slowly.
ちょっとゆっくりだけ、ちょっとだけ動かすよ
it hurts?
痛い?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
This is amazing.
これは、すごいな
The inside is full of folds.
ひだだらけだ、さっきの中は
It has a healthy salmon pink color.
健康的なサーモンピンクの色してますよ
Salmon pink?
サーモンピンク?
Yes, it's a healthy pussy.
うん、健康的なおまんこです
Okay, so let's take it out a little bit.
よし、じゃあ、ちょっと抜いてみよう
Well then, Ya-chan, let's talk about that again.
じゃあ、やーちゃん、それちょっとまた、
Shall we put it in?
入れてみようか
I put it in.
入れた
It's like this.
こんな感じですよ
Wow, that's amazing.
え、すげー
I saw it for the first time.
初めて見た
That's amazing, isn't it?
すごいでしょ
Go as far as you can and then
できるところまで行って、そこで、
You don't have to release it slowly,
ゆっくり出し切りなくていいから、
Try taking it in and out slowly.
ゆっくり出し入れしてごらん
Let's take it out for a second and put it back in.
ちょっと、ちょっと抜いて、また入れてみよう
And then I put it back in and yeah yeah yeah yeah.
で、また入れて、そうそうそうそう
Take it slow.
ゆっくりやってごらん
I'm a mental drinker.
俺、精神飲みですわ
Okay, then let's take it out slowly.
よし、じゃあ、ゆっくり抜いてみようか
Please open it.
開けてごらん
Yes, thank you very much.
はーい、ありがとうございました
Shall we go take a bath?
お風呂行こうか
Yeah.
うん